Guide to the Francis J. McNamara papers, 1928-1997
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 2: National Security, 1976-1997; (60 boxes)
  - Enveloped Materials: CISPES (folder 1 of 2), 1981-1991 (Folder 1, Box 172)
  - Enveloped Materials: CISPES (folder 2 of 2), 1981-1991 (Folder 2, Box 172)
  - Enveloped Materials: Handal's F. and S. Mex Office - ISHEE, 1981 (Folder 3, Box 172)
    McNamara, Security and Intelligence Foundation
  - Enveloped Materials: Nicarag. Vote, February 1990 (Folder 4, Box 172)
    Nicaragua, Political Advisor Argentina
  - Enveloped Materials: Cent. Amer., 1987 (Folder 5, Box 172)
    Council for Inter-American Security
  - Enveloped Materials: CISPES - CONV's, 1990 (Folder 6, Box 172)
    The Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador
  - Enveloped materials: HASENFUS, 1986 (Folder 7, Box 172)
    Hasenfus, Nicaragua, United States Global Security Council
  - Enveloped Materials: CISPES - TERROR, 1982-1987 (Folder 8, Box 172)
  - Enveloped Materials: HJC - CISPES (folder 1 of 2), 1985-1991 (Folder 9, Box 172)
  - Enveloped Materials: HJC - CISPES (folder 2 of 2), 1985-1991 (Folder 1, Box 173)
  - Enveloped Materials: Gray, 1976 (Folder 2, Box 173)
  - Enveloped Materials: F-M Regan Pardon, 1989 (Folder 3, Box 173)
    Reagan
  - Enveloped Materials: Huston Plan, ca. 1976 (Folder 4, Box 173)
    Notes
  - Enveloped Materials: FOFBI, ca. 1976 (Folder 5, Box 173)
    Friends of the FBI
  - Enveloped Materials: PRO-INDICTS1, 1977 (Folder 6, Box 173)
    FBI, Heritage Foundation
  - Enveloped Materials: PROS TEAM - FELT MILLER. JUDGE U.S.A. TTY's., 1979 (Folder 7, Box 173)
    Newspaper Clippings, Trials. United States vs. Gray, Felt, Miller
  - Enveloped Materials: WIRE TAP - FBI - CIA book, 1980 (Folder 8, Box 173)
    American Bar Association, CIA, FBI, Wiretapping
  - Enveloped Materials: G-F-M indicts, 1978 (Folder 9, Box 173)
    United States vs. Gray, Felt, Miller
  - Enveloped Materials: Felt-Miller, 1978 (Folder 10, Box 173)
  - The Erosion of Law Enforcement Intelligence and Its Impact on the Public Security, 1978 (Folder 11, Box 173)
    Intelligence, Judiciary Committee, Police
  - Espionage cases, 1986-1989 (Folder 12, Box 173)
  - Executive Order's classification, 1978-1983 (Folder 13, Box 173)
    Department of Justice, Intelligence, National Security, Reagan
  - Executive Order-10450 FFD employee security, 1977-1994 (Folder 14, Box 173)
    Federal Employment, Intelligence, Security
  - Extremism Targets the Prisons: An ADL Special Report, 1986 (Folder 1, Box 174)
    Anti-Defamation League, Political Extremists
  - FALN [Fuerzas Armadas de Liberacion Nacional], 1977-1984 (Folder 2, Box 174)
    Puerto Rico, Armed Forces of National Liberation
  - FARA [Foreign Agents Registration Act], 1982-1990 (Folder 3, Box 174)
    Foreign Agents Registration Act
  - FARA-investigation, 1980-1989 (Folder 4, Box 174)
  - Farber, Myron, 1978 (Folder 5, Box 174)
  - FBI, 1976-1982 (Folder 6, Box 174)
    Freedom of Information, Newspaper Clippings
  - FBI, 1976-1982 (Folder 7, Box 174)
    FBI Proposals to Amend the Freedom of Information Act
  - FBI numbers and qualification, 1983-1984 (Folder 8, Box 174)
    FBI Training, FBI Application Process
  - FBI - FOIA-requested documents, 1978 (Folder 9, Box 174)
  - FBI-damage - general, 1977 (Folder 10, Box 174)
    Freedom of Information Act, Intelligence Techniques
  - FBI-domestic intelligence failures, 1982-1983 (Folder 11, Box 174)
    Intelligence, Wiretapping
  - FBI-files-data-computers, 1979-1988 (Folder 1, Box 175)
    Courts, FBI, LaRouche
  - FBI guidelines FCI, 1980 (Folder 2, Box 175)
    FBI, Guidelines, Intelligence Gathering
  - FBI guidelines: domestic security - Levi, 1976 (Folder 3, Box 175)
    Attorney General Levi, Domestic Security, FBI, Guidelines, Lawton, Mary
  - FBI guidelines-Smith: domestic security, 1983 (Folder 4, Box 175)
    Department of Justice, Domestic Security, Guidelines, FBI, Terrorism
  - FBI Guidelines/Informants, 1977-1980 (Folder 5, Box 175)
    Domestic Security, Newspaper Clippings, Paid Informants
  - FBI morale, 1978 (Folder 6, Box 175)
    Scandals, Kelley, Webster
  - FBI personnel, 1979-1986 (Folder 7, Box 175)
    Congressional Records, Deaths, Female Officers, Newspaper Clippings
  - FBI-terrorism, 1977-1989 (Folder 8, Box 175)
    Domestic Security, Newspaper Clippings, Terrorism
  - Federal Law Enforcement Officers' Association, 1978-1982 (Folder 9, Box 175)
    FLEOA, Newsletter, Washington, D.C.
  - Felt-Miller, 1981 (Folder 10, Box 175)
    Felt-Miller exhibit no. 99 A USDC-DC criminal no. 78-000179
  - First Principles No. 2 (Vols. 3-6), 1978-1980 (Folder 1, Box 176)
    Civil Liberties, National Security
  - First Principles (PNSCL of ACLU and CNSS), 1985-1987 (Folder 2, Box 176)
    American Civil Liberties Union, Center for National Security Studies
  - First Principles, 1981-1984 (Folder 3, Box 176)
    Heritage Foundation, Intelligence
  - First Principles, 1981-1984 (Folder 4, Box 176)
    Detente, Reagan
  - First Principles, 1988-1992 (Folder 5, Box 176)
    Covert Operations, Paramilitary
  - First Principles, 1988-1992 (Folder 6, Box 176)
    Civil Liberties, Persian Gulf Crisis
  - FLEOA, 1989-1991 (Folder 7, Box 176)
    Federal Law Enforcement Officers Association
  - FLT 007, 1983 (Folder 8, Box 176)
    Korean Air Lines Flight 007, September 1, 1983
  - FLT 007, 1983-1988 (Folder 1, Box 177)
    Korean Air Lines Flight 007, KAL, (9/1/83)
  - FMLN-FDR, 1988-1989 (Folder 2, Box 177)
    El Salvador, Roosevelt, Franklin Delano
  - FMLN-FDR, 1988-1989 (Folder 3, Box 177)
  - FOIA, 1983-1993 (Folder 4, Box 177)
  - FOIA, 1983-1993 (Folder 5, Box 177)
  - FOIA, 1976-1983 (Folder 6, Box 177)
  - FOIA, 1976-1983 (Folder 7, Box 177)
  - FOIA-general, 1977 (Folder 8, Box 177)
  - FOIA bills (Chaffee), 1978-1981 (Folder 9, Box 177)
    Freedom of Information Act, Barry Goldwater
  - D'Amato [Alfonse] FOIA bill and testimony, 1981 (Folder 10, Box 177)
    Freedom of Information Act, Chaffee, Goldwater,
  - FOIA-FBI, ca. 1980s (Folder 11, Box 177)
    Freedom of Information Act, McNamara's notes
  - FOIA-media, 1977-1982 (Folder 12, Box 177)
  - FOIA - Reagan Administration, 1981-1983 (Folder 1, Box 178)
    Freedom of Information Act, Reagan, Ronald
  - FOIA-requests, 1978-1985 (Folder 2, Box 178)
  - FOIA-Jonestown, 1978-1981 (Folder 3, Box 178)
    Mass Murder Suicide, Guyana
  - Fonda, Jane, 1982-1993 (Folder 4, Box 178)
    Newspaper Clippings, Veterans, Vietnam
  - Foreign Intelligence Book Series, ca.1980s (Folder 5, Box 178)
    "The Secret War in Central America", "The Shadow War"
  - Former secrets: government secrets made public through FOIA, 1982 (Folder 6, Box 178)
    Campaign for Public Rights
  - France, 1980-1987 (Folder 7, Box 178)
    Espionage, Soviet Spies
  - Frank M. Johnson, 1977 (Folder 8, Box 178)
    FBI, President Carter
  - Friendly espionage, 1976-1982 (Folder 9, Box 178)
    Israel, South Korea
  - Gandhi, Rajiv, 1989-1991 (Folder 10, Box 178)
    Assassination, India
  - Gary T. Rowe (FBI), 1978-1983 (Folder 11, Box 178)
    FBI, Rowe, Gary
  - Gates, Robert M., 1970-1994 (Folder 12, Box 178)
    Department of Defense
  - General information (AFIO), 1982-1986 (Folder 13, Box 178)
    Association of Former Intelligence Officers
  - General James L. Dozier, 1981-1982 (Folder 14, Box 178)
    Kidnapping, Italy, Red Brigades
  - General accounting office and FBI, 1976-1982 (Folder 15, Box 178)
    Espionage, GAO, Information Security, Soviet Union
  - General accounting office and FBI, 1976-1982 (Folder 1, Box 179)
  - General Services Administration - Special Announcement, 1987 (Folder 2, Box 179)
    Strategic Directions in Physical Security
  - Gilbert, Otto A., 1982 (Folder 3, Box 179)
    Conspiracy, Espionage, Newspaper Clippings
  - Global Strategy Council or Network, 1985-1986 (Folder 4, Box 179)
    Global Strategy Network, GSC, GSN
  - Global Strategy Council, 1981-1985 (Folder 5, Box 179)
    GSC
  - Government Lawsuits, 1980-1995 (Folder 6, Box 179)
  - Government Lawsuits, 1980-1995 (Folder 7, Box 179)
  - Government Lawsuits, 1978-1995 (Folder 8, Box 179)
  - Government Lawsuits, 1978-1995 (Folder 9, Box 179)
  - Grant (Wraga) paper, 1986 (Folder 1, Box 180)
    McNamara, Nathan Hale Institute, Soviet Disinformation
  - Gravier, David - Jacobo Timerman, 1977-1988 (Folder 2, Box 180)
    Argentina, Guerrillas, Illegal Financing
  - Graymail, 1979-1980 (Folder 3, Box 180)
    Classified Information, Trials, Senator Biden
  - Grenada Invasion, 1983-1988 (Folder 4, Box 180)
    Grenada, Newspaper Clippings, Reagan
  - Grenada Invasion, 1983-1988 (Folder 5, Box 180)
  - Grenada Invasion, 1982-1983 (Folder 6, Box 180)
  - Grenada Invasion, 1982-1983 (Folder 7, Box 180)
  - Grenada Invasion, 1983-1984 (Folder 8, Box 180)
  - Griffin Bell, 1977-1984 (Folder 9, Box 180)
    Attorney General, Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act, Newspaper Clippings
  - GSA, 1977-1982 (Folder 10, Box 180)
    General Services Administration
  - The Guardian, April 2, 1980 (Folder 1, Box 181)
  - Guidelines-SST Hearings, 1981-1982 (Folder 2, Box 181)
    Senate Subcommittee on Security and Terrorism
  - Guidelines on criminal investigations, 1976-1981 (Folder 3, Box 181)
  - Haig, Alexander M., 1980-1983 (Folder 4, Box 181)
    General Haig, Alexander M., Secretary of State
  - Haig, Alexander M., 1980-1981 (Folder 5, Box 181)
    Secretary of State, Reagan Administration
  - Haiti, 1993-1995 (Folder 6, Box 181)
    Haiti
  - Hale Foundation - S. 391, 1981 (Folder 7, Box 181)
    Hale, Nathan, Hale Foundation
  - Hale Foundation, 1977-1981 (Folder 8, Box 181)
  - Hale Foundation, 1977-1981 (Folder 9, Box 181)
  - Hale Foundation/Nathan Hale Institute, 1982-1994 (Folder 10, Box 181)
  - Hale Foundation/Nathan Hale Institute, 1982-1994 (Folder 11, Box 181)
  - Hale Foundation and Nathan Hale Institute Publishers, 1980s (Folder 1, Box 182)
  - Hale Foundation and Nathan Hale Institute Publishers, 1980s (Folder 2, Box 182)
  - Hale Foundation-policy board, 1981 (Folder 3, Box 182)
  - Hale [Foundation]-mailed appeals (Folder 4, Box 182)
  - Hale [Foundation] personnel, 1980s (Folder 5, Box 182)
  - Hale [Foundation]-program, 1978-1982 (Folder 6, Box 182)
  - Hale [Foundation]-publicity, 1981 (Folder 7, Box 182)
  - Hale - Publications, 1997 (Folder 8, Box 182)
  - Hale Foundation - "U.S. Counterintelligence Today", 1980s (Folder 9, Box 182)
  - Hale - Public (Annual Reports), 1987-1989 (Folder 1, Box 183)
  - Hale Foundation - General, 1977-1981 (Folder 2, Box 183)
  - Hale - FOIA - McNamara, 1980s (Folder 3, Box 183)
    Freedom of Information act, Hale, Nathan, McNamara, Francis
  - Hall, James W, III; Craig D. Konkle, 1988-1989 (Folder 4, Box 183)
    Espionage, Intelligence, Soviet Union
  - HALP TEST - Hearing Gallery [folder 1 of 4], November 19, 1993 (Folder 5, Box 183)
    Halperin, Morton H.
  - HALP TEST - Hearing Gallery [folder 2 of 4], November 19, 1993 (Folder 6, Box 183)
  - HALP TEST - Hearing Gallery [folder 3 of 4], November 19, 1993 (Folder 7, Box 183)
  - HALP TEST - Hearing Gallery [folder 4 of 4], November 19, 1993 (Folder 8, Box 183)
  - HALPERIN SUIT (wiretap) [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Folder 9, Box 183)
    Halperin, Kissinger, Lawsuits, Wiretapping
  - HALPERIN SUIT (wiretap) [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Folder 10, Box 183)
  - Morton Halperin, 1993 (Folder 11, Box 183)
  - HALP Notes, 1979-1983 (Folder 1, Box 184)
  - Halperin Doc.s - McNamara Statement [folder 1 of 2], 1994 (Folder 2, Box 184)
  - Halperin Doc.s - McNamara Statement [folder 2 of 2], 1994-1996 (Folder 3, Box 184)
  - Halperin Testimony - Videos, 1993 (Folder 4, Box 184)
  - Harper, James D., 1983-1984 (Folder 5, Box 184)
  - Hart, Gary, 1983-1987 (Folder 6, Box 184)
  - Hatch Act, 1976-1993 (Folder 7, Box 184)
    Hatch, Orin
  - Hays [Wayne L.]-House Reform, 1976-1977 (Folder 8, Box 184)
    House of Representatives, Management, Newspaper Clippings
  - Hays [Wayne L.]-Ray, 1976 (Folder 9, Box 184)
    Affair, Newspaper Clippings, Scandals
  - Hays [Wayne L.]-Ray, 1976 (Folder 1, Box 185)
  - Rep. Hays, Wayne [L.]-Huber, 1976-1977 (Folder 2, Box 185)
  - Hearst, Patricia - trial, 1976 (Folder 3, Box 185)
    Hearst, Patricia
  - Hearst, Patricia - trial, 1976 (Folder 4, Box 185)
  - Hearst, Patricia trial, 1976-1982 (Folder 5, Box 185)
  - Helmich, Joseph George, 1981 (Folder 6, Box 185)
  - Helms, Richard - Congress communications, 1976-1980 (Folder 7, Box 185)
    Official Letters
  - Heritage Foundation, 1982 (Folder 8, Box 185)
    The High Frontier
  - Herman, Rudolph Albert, 1980 (Folder 9, Box 185)
    CIA, FBI, KGB
  - High Frontier, 1988-1991 (Folder 10, Box 185)
    SDI, SDIO
  - High Frontier, 1988-1991 (Folder 11, Box 185)
  - High Frontier-a project of the Heritage Foundation, 1982; Book, Star Wars (SDI) (Folder 12, Box 185)
    Defense
  - High-tech exports, 1982-1985 (Folder 1, Box 186)
    Newspaper Clippings, Technology Leaks
  - Hobson case, 1984-1985 (Folder 2, Box 186)
    Civil Rights, FBI, Hobson vs. Wilson
  - Hollywood - Political, 1977-1985 (Folder 3, Box 186)
  - Holocaust, 1978-1985 (Folder 4, Box 186)
    NAZI, WWII
  - Hoover, J. Edgar and Pearl Harbor, 1980s (Folder 5, Box 186)
  - Hoover private file, 1983 (Folder 6, Box 186)
  - Hosenball, Mark - Stephen R. Weissman, 1976-1991 (Folder 7, Box 186)
    CIA, Hosenball, Information Leak
  - Howard, Ed Lee, 1989-1995 (Folder 8, Box 186)
    CIA, Espionage, Fugitive Agents
  - House Intelligence Committee (permanent-select) - Edward Boland, 1977-1985 (Folder 9, Box 186)
    Arms Race, CIA, Intelligence
  - House Intelligence Committee (permanent-select) ([Edward P.] Boland), 1977-1988 (Folder 10, Box 186)
    Congressional Records, Intelligence Committee
  - Hugel, Max [CIA spy chief], 1981-1982 (Folder 11, Box 186)
  - Hughes, Ryan (covert action), 1980 (Folder 12, Box 186)
  - Human Rights, 1977-1978 (Folder 13, Box 186)
    Prison Camps, Soviet Dissidents
  - Humphrey [Ronald Louis]-[David] Truong, 1978-1986 (Folder 14, Box 186)
    CIA, Espionage, FBI, Vietnam
  - India, 1985 (Folder 15, Box 186)
    India, Spy Scandal
  - Indira Gandhi, 1984-1989 (Folder 1, Box 187)
    Assassination, India, Sikhs
  - Inman, Ray, 1993-1994 (Folder 2, Box 187)
    CIA, Defense Secretary, Clinton, Presidential Appointments
  - Inman, Bobby Ray, 1980-1983 (Folder 3, Box 187)
  - The Coalition Insider, 1978-1981 (Folder 4, Box 187)
    Coalition for Peace Through Strength
  - Institute for Policy Studies, 1980s (Folder 5, Box 187)
    El Salvador, Latin America, Vietnam
  - Inquiry [Magazine], 1978 (Folder 6, Box 187)
    Agee, Phillip, CIA,
  - Intelligence failures (Iran, etc.), 1978-1979 (Folder 7, Box 187)
    Cuba, South Africa, Soviet Union, U2
  - Intelligence failures (Iran, etc.), 1978-1981 (Folder 8, Box 187)
    Foreign Policy, Intelligence, Newspaper Clippings
  - Intelligence - General, 1976-1988 (Folder 9, Box 187)
  - Intelligence (UPA-FILS-FIBS-ETC), 1984-1985 (Folder 10, Box 187)
    Foreign Intelligence
  - Intelligence oversight, 1976-1979 (Folder 11, Box 187)
    Congressional Oversight, Intelligence
  - Intelligence Oversight Act, 1980 (Folder 1, Box 188)
    Intelligence Agencies, Oversight
  - INS-Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1983-1990 (Folder 2, Box 188)
    Aliens, Political Asylum
  - Internal Revenue Service (request for forms), 1980 (Folder 3, Box 188)
    Department of the Treasury, Invoice, McNamara
  - Invitation to a lecture with Kathleen Bailey, 1987 (Folder 4, Box 188)
    Heritage Foundation, Soviet Disinformation
  - Iran, 1976-1979 (Folder 5, Box 188)
    Iranian Revolution, Shah, Carter, Khomeini
  - Iran, 1977-1982 (Folder 6, Box 188)
  - International [terrorist] control measures (for nations), 1976-1982 (Folder 7, Box 188)
    Torture, Britain, Spain, Hijacking
  - Iran - US embassy seizure, 1979 (Folder 8, Box 188)
    Iran, Terrorism
  - Iran - US embassy seizure, 1979 (Folder 9, Box 188)
  - Iran embassy rescue of hostages fails: Desert One, 1980 (Folder 10, Box 188)
  - Iran Hostages, 1980-1981 (Folder 11, Box 188)
  - Iran - Shah, 1976-1979 (Folder 12, Box 188)
    Coup, Iran, Soviet Union
  - Irish Republican Army, 1974-1995 (Folder 13, Box 188)
    IRA, Terrorism
  - Irish Republican Army, 1978-1990 (Folder 14, Box 188)
  - Irish Republican Army, 1978-1990 (Folder 1, Box 189)
    IRA, Sinn Fein
  - IRS-forms--anti-intelligence groups, 1976-1978 (Folder 2, Box 189)
  - Israel, 1984-1992 (Folder 3, Box 189)
    Israel
  - Israel, 1984-1992 (Folder 4, Box 189)
  - Israel, 1986-1988 (Folder 5, Box 189)
  - Israeli-Uganda attack, 1976-1977 (Folder 6, Box 189)
    Entebbe, Israel
  - Italy, 1978-1981 (Folder 7, Box 189)
    Italy
  - Italy - Aldo Moro, 1976-1987 (Folder 8, Box 189)
    Italy, Moro, Aldo
  - ITT, 1978 (Folder 9, Box 189)
    International Telephone and Telegraph Corp., CIA
  - Jamestown Foundation, 1986 (Folder 1, Box 190)
    National Security
  - Japan-'95 subway gassing (aum supreme truth), 1995 (Folder 2, Box 190)
    Terrorism, Japan
  - Japanese, 1981-1995 (Folder 3, Box 190)
    Japan
  - Japanese, 1982-1995 (Folder 4, Box 190)
  - Japanese, 1982-1995 (Folder 5, Box 190)
  - Japanese Red Army, 1977-1978 (Folder 6, Box 190)
  - JBAKC, 1979-1981 (Folder 7, Box 190)
    John Brown Book Club, Weather Underground Organization, WUO
  - Jeffries, Randy M., 1985 (Folder 8, Box 190)
    Espionage, Newspaper Clippings
  - Jennings-Markward, 1980s (Folder 9, Box 190)
    Conversation with Frank McNamara
  - JFK-MLK - House Assassinations Committee, 1977-1983 (Folder 10, Box 190)
    Assassination, Kennedy, McNamara, Newspaper Clippings
  - JFK-MLK - House Assassinations Committee, 1977-1983 (Folder 11, Box 190)
  - Jonestown, 1978-1988 (Folder 12, Box 190)
    Guyana
  - Jonestown, 1978-1981 (Folder 13, Box 190)
  - Kampiles, William P. - Soviet Mole, 1978-1979 (Folder 1, Box 191)
    Soviet Spy
  - Karch, John J., 1979-1985 (Folder 2, Box 191)
    "The Soviet Union" prepared for the World Encyclopedia of the Press
  - Karch, John J., 1979-1985 (Folder 3, Box 191)
    Correspondence, National Defense University
  - Kearney, John etc. civil suits, 1977 (Folder 4, Box 191)
    FBI, Lawsuits, Terrorism
  - KGB connection, 1981-1982 (Folder 5, Box 191)
    An Investigation into Soviet Espionage Operations in North America
  - Kidnap victims - Chowchilla, 1976-1977 (Folder 6, Box 191)
    Terrorism, Kidnapping
  - King, Martin Luther, 1979-1995 (Folder 7, Box 191)
    Chowchilla Kidnapping Trial
  - King, Martin Luther, 1979-1995 (Folder 8, Box 191)
  - Ku Klux Klan, 1990-1995 (Folder 9, Box 191)
    KKK
  - KKK riot - Washington - against the KKK, 1982 (Folder 10, Box 191)
    Ku Klux Klan
  - KKK and white hate, 1976-1995 (Folder 11, Box 191)
  - KKK and white hate, 1976-1995 (Folder 12, Box 191)
  - Korean-Rangoon, 1983-1985 (Folder 1, Box 192)
    Burma, Myanmar, Bombing, Korea
  - Korean War, 1992-1995 (Folder 2, Box 192)
  - Lance, Bert, 1970-1980 (Folder 3, Box 192)
    Lance, Bert
  - L.A. riot, 1992 (Folder 4, Box 192)
    Los Angeles
  - L.A. riot, 1992 (Folder 5, Box 192)
  - L.A. riot, 1992 (Folder 6, Box 192)
  - L.A. riot, 1992 (Folder 7, Box 192)
  - L.A. riot, 1992 (Folder 8, Box 192)
  - L.A. riot, 1992 (Folder 9, Box 192)
  - Lake, Anthony, 1995-1997 (Folder 10, Box 192)
    CIA, Clinton, Espionage, Hiss
  - Landau, Saul - Washington Post, 1981 (Folder 1, Box 193)
    Landau, Saul, Newspaper
  - Legacy, 1980s (Folder 2, Box 193)
    Anti-Communism, Blacklisting, Cold War, Hollywood
  - Legal harassment articles, ca. 1978 (Folder 3, Box 193)
    Demonstrations, FBI, Kearney
  - Les Aspin-Perry, 1993-1995 (Folder 4, Box 193)
    Defense Secretary, Perry, William
  - Letelier [Orlando]-Moffitt, 1976-1980 (Folder 5, Box 193)
    Letelier, Orlando
  - Letelier-Moffitt, 1980-1995 (Folder 6, Box 193)
  - Letelier-Moffitt, 1980-1995 (Folder 7, Box 193)
  - Levchenko, Stanislav A., 1983 (Folder 8, Box 193)
    The Spy Who Knew Too Much
  - Libya, 1982-1989 (Folder 9, Box 193)
  - Libya, 1982-1989 (Folder 10, Box 193)
  - Libya assassination squad, 1981-1982 (Folder 1, Box 194)
    Libya, Assassination
  - Libya-(Tafoya), 1979-1990 (Folder 2, Box 194)
  - Lingo - language, language education, 1980-1981 (Folder 3, Box 194)
    Language
  - Lonetree, Sgt. Clayton J., 1987 (Folder 4, Box 194)
    Lonetree, Sgt. Clayton
  - Los Macheteros (and Wells Fargo, Conn. robbery), 1983-1989 (Folder 5, Box 194)
    Los Macheteros
  - Lt. Cooke, Christopher, 1981 (Folder 6, Box 194)
    Cooke, Christopher
  - MacArthur Foundation, 1987-1995 (Folder 7, Box 194)
    MacArthur Foundation
  - Marine Guards-Embassy, 1987-1988 (Folder 8, Box 194)
    US Embassy in Soviet Union
  - Martin, Dave, 1978-1995 (Folder 9, Box 194)
    Correspondence, Federal Employee Security Act, Internal Security
  - Martin, Dave, 1978-1995 (Folder 10, Box 194)
    The Federal Employee Security Program: A Critical Appraisal
  - Mayer, Norman David, 1982 (Folder 11, Box 194)
    Mayer, Norman
  - Meese, Edwin H., 1984-1988 (Folder 12, Box 194)
    Meese, Edwin
  - Meese, Edwin, 1980s (Folder 1, Box 195)
  - Meese, Edwin, 1980s (Folder 2, Box 195)
  - Meese Speeches, 1980s (Folder 3, Box 195)
  - Meese Speeches, 1976-1985 (Folder 4, Box 195)
  - Memphis, 1978 (Folder 5, Box 195)
    Memphis, Tennessee
  - Mexico, 1976-1978 (Folder 6, Box 195)
    Mexico
  - Mexico, Colosio - assassinations, 1994 (Folder 7, Box 195)
    Colosio, Donaldo, Mexico
  - Micronesia, 1976-1978 (Folder 8, Box 195)
    Micronesia
  - Miller, Wm. G (FBI) and Ogorodikova, 1980s (Folder 9, Box 195)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Articles, 1980s (Folder 10, Box 195)
    Newspaper
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Articles, 1978-1988 (Folder 11, Box 195)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Articles, 1980s (Folder 12, Box 195)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Articles, 1980s (Folder 13, Box 195)
  - MoLuccans, 1977-1978 (Folder 14, Box 195)
    Indonesia
  - Morison, Samuel, Loring, 1980s (Folder 15, Box 195)
    Espionage, Trials
  - Moscow - Embassy, 1976-1987 (Folder 16, Box 195)
    Cold War, Soviet Union, Embassies, USSR
  - Moscow - Cuba - Nicaragua Interplay, 1989-1991 (Folder 17, Box 195)
    Cold War, Latin America, Cuba, Nicaragua, Soviet Union, USSR
  - Mountbatten, 1979 (Folder 18, Box 195)
    Mountbatten, Earl
  - Move (Phila.), 1985-1995 (Folder 19, Box 195)
    Philadelphia
  - Muhammad Ali Hammadi, 1987-1989 (Folder 1, Box 196)
  - National Intelligence Study Center - Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Folder 2, Box 196)
    NISC
  - National Security Archive, 1980s (Folder 3, Box 196)
    NSA
  - National Strategy Information Center, Inc and Barnett, 1980s (Folder 4, Box 196)
    NSIC
  - Nazi - KKK, 1980s (Folder 5, Box 196)
    Klu Klux Klan
  - Nazi - KKK Violence (Greensboro etc.) (Folder 6, Box 196)
  - NCLC La Rouche, 1983-1990 (Folder 7, Box 196)
    National Caucus of Labor Committees, La Rouche, Lyndon
  - NCLC - (La Rouche), 1976-1983 (Folder 8, Box 196)
  - NCLC - (La Rouche), 1977-1987 (Folder 9, Box 196)
  - [Newspaper], May 30, 1997 (Folder 10, Box 196)
  - Nicaragua, 1978-1993 (Folder 1, Box 197)
    Contras, Government Spending, Washington Lobby on Latin America
  - Nicaragua, 1978-1993 (Folder 2, Box 197)
    Contras, Council for Inter-American Security, Newspaper Clippings
  - Nicaragua, 1980-1990 (Folder 3, Box 197)
    Contras, Newspaper Clippings, Reagan, Sandanistas
  - Nicaragua, 1980-1990 (Folder 4, Box 197)
  - Nicaragua, 1980-1990 (Folder 5, Box 197)
  - Nicaragua, 1978-1985 (Folder 6, Box 197)
  - Nicaragua, 1980s (Folder 7, Box 197)
  - Nicholson, Harold J., 1996-1997 (Folder 8, Box 197)
    CIA, Espionage
  - Nixon-Truman-FDR etc., 1980 (Folder 9, Box 197)
    Roosevelt, Franklin Delano
  - Non-CISPES aid-agitation, 1981-1989 (Folder 10, Box 197)
  - North, Oliver L., 1990s (Folder 1, Box 198)
    North, Oliver